William Safire Papers
William Safire Papers
- "On Language" files
  - Research files, Safire's original folder titles were retained.
    - Music critic-ese (Box 160)
    - Muskeggy (Box 160)
    - Mutual and Balanced Force Reductions (MBFR) (Box 160)
    - Muzzleable (Box 160)
    - My ambassador (Box 160)
    - My bad (Box 160)
    - Myriad (Box 160)
    - Myself (Box 160)
    - Mysterium iniquitas (Box 160)
    - Mythology metaphors (Box 160)
    - 'N' (Box 160)
    - Naked short (Box 160)
    - Name for a word common in writing but not in speaking (Box 160)
    - Name that league (Box 160)
    - Name that plunge (Box 160)
    - Named for/named after (Box 160)
    - Names (Box 160)
    - Names - funny (Box 160)
    - Names for nowadays (Box 160)
    - Names for nowadays, 3 folders (Box 161)
    - Nanny/manny (Box 161)
    - Narrative (Box 161)
    - Nation (Box 161)
    - National museum of language (Box 161)
    - National Security Presidential Directive (NSPD) (Box 161)
    - NATO-ese (Box 161)
    - Nautical metaphors (Box 161)
    - Naval metaphors (Box 161)
    - Near abroad (Box 161)
    - Near terms (Box 161)
    - Necked down (Box 161)
    - Needed cleaned (Box 161)
    - Needed words (Box 161)
    - Negative (Box 161)
    - Neither...nor...nor (Box 161)
    - Neo (Box 161)
    - Neo-creo (Box 161)
    - Neologisms (Box 161)
    - Neology (Box 162)
    - Neorealism (Box 162)
    - Netroots (Box 162)
    - Networking (Box 162)
    - Neuroethics (Box 162)
    - Never say never (Box 162)
    - New black (Box 162)
    - New colors (Box 162)
    - New era thinking (Box 162)
    - New new thing (Box 162)
    - New showbiz words (Box 162)
    - New urbanism (Box 162)
    - New words (Box 162)
    - New world dictionary (Box 162)
    - New yawk twalk - New York talk (Box 162)
    - New Yorker magazine mistakes (Box 162)
    - New Yorkerisms (Box 162)
    - News (Box 162)
    - Newsletter-ese (Box 162)
    - Newswords (Box 162)
    - Newtonian linguistics (Box 162)
    - Next (Box 162)
    - Next big thing (Box 163)
    - Nice guys finish last - Durocher, Leo (Box 163)
    - Niggardly (Box 163)
    - Night letters (Box 163)
    - -nik - meister (Box 163)
    - Ninth (Box 163)
    - Nitpick (Box 163)
    - Nitpicks (Box 163)
    - Nitty gritty (Box 163)
    - Nixon, Richard - non-resignation speech (Box 163)
    - Nixon, Richard - tapes (Box 163)
    - Nixon, Richard - war on cancer (Box 163)
    - No brainer (Box 163)
    - No comment (Box 163)
    - No man's land (Box 163)
    - No more fries - freedom fries (Box 163)
    - No, no, no, no, no! (Box 163)
    - Nomenclature (Box 163)
    - Nomination acceptance speeches, 2 folders (Box 163)
    - None (Box 164)
    - Nonhostile deaths (Box 164)
    - Nonlinear battlefield (Box 164)
    - Nonplussed (Box 164)
    - Normalcy/normality (Box 164)
    - North - south (Box 164)
    - Not (Box 164)
    - Not for profit (Box 164)
    - Not for worry (Box 164)
    - Noted/notorious/notoriety/notable (Box 164)
    - Nounification of verbs (Box 164)
    - Nouveau riche (Box 164)
    - Nov schmoz ka pop (Box 164)
    - Nuance (Box 164)
    - Nuclear - pronunciation (Box 164)
    - Nuclear option (Box 164)
    - Number symbol - pound (#) (Box 164)
    - Numeracy - visuacy (Box 164)
    - Nutritionist v dietitian (Box 164)
    - -o (Box 164)
    - O.K. (Box 164)
    - Oars in the water (Box 164)
    - Oath of office (Box 164)
    - Obama-rama (Box 164)
    - Obama, Barack (Box 164)
    - Obama, Barack - inaugural address (Box 164)
    - Obama, Barack - speeches (Box 164)
    - Obituaries (Box 164)
    - Observant v practicing (Box 164)
    - Occupied territories (Box 165)
    - October surprise (Box 165)
    - Oddities (Box 165)
    - Odious debt (Box 165)
    - Of (Box 165)
    - Off and on (Box 165)
    - Off load (Box 165)
    - Off of (Box 165)
    - Off the dime (Box 165)
    - Off the record (Box 165)
    - Off the wall (Box 165)
    - Official - formal - legal (Box 165)
    - Offshoring (Box 165)
    - Often wrong but never in doubt (Box 165)
    - Okeydoke (Box 165)
    - Old Europe (Box 165)
    - Old slang (Box 165)
    - -ologies (Box 165)
    - Olympiad (Box 165)
    - Olympic-ese (Box 165)
    - Omni (Box 165)
    - On all fours (Box 165)
    - On the edge (Box 165)
    - On the fritz (Box 166)
    - On the ground (Box 166)
    - On the line (Box 166)
    - One fell swoop (Box 166)
    - One of those (Box 166)
    - One off (Box 166)
    - One word (Box 166)
    - Online/on-line (Box 166)
    - Onomastics (Box 166)
    - Op-ed derived (Box 166)
    - Operationalize - anonymize (Box 166)
    - Opposites (Box 166)
    - Optics - boardroom-ese (Box 166)
    - Oracle (Box 166)
    - Organic (Box 166)
    - Orgasmic (Box 166)
    - -oriented (Box 166)
    - Original word to abbreviation to new word (Box 166)
    - Origins (Box 166)
    - Osage v ozark (Box 166)
    - Otherize (Box 166)
    - Out (Box 166)
    - Out of luck (Box 166)
    - Out of touch (Box 166)
    - Out of whack (Box 166)
    - Out there (Box 166)
    - Out to lunch (Box 166)
    - Outcompete (Box 166)
    - Outdated expressions (Box 166)
    - Outland (Box 166)
    - Outsource (Box 166)
    - Outtake (Box 167)
    - Over the internet (Box 167)
    - Over the top (Box 167)
    - Over- (Box 167)
    - Overnight (Box 167)
    - Overwatch (Box 167)
    - Ox is in the ditch (Box 167)
    - Oxford English Dictionary (OED) (Box 167)
    - Oxymorons (Box 167)
    - P8/G8 (Box 167)
    - Paesano/paisan (Box 167)
    - Paleoconservatives (Box 167)
    - Palindromes, 2 folders (Box 167)
    - Pallet (Box 167)
    - Pandering (Box 167)
    - Pantywaist (Box 167)
    - Papal (Box 167)
    - Paperboard (Box 167)
    - Paradigm (Box 167)
    - Paraleipsis v apophasis (Box 167)
    - Part and parcel (Box 167)
    - Partial-birth abortion (Box 167)
    - Pass the password (Box 167)
    - Passengers (Box 167)
    - Passing strange (Box 167)
    - Passwords (Box 167)
    - Past participles (Box 168)
    - Patriate (Box 168)
    - Patronize (Box 168)
    - Pax (Box 168)
    - Payback politics (Box 168)
    - Peace divided (Box 168)
    - Peace loving (Box 168)
    - Peaceable (Box 168)
    - Peanut gallery (Box 168)
    - Peck's bad boy (Box 168)
    - Pecs (Box 168)
    - Pedal to the metal (Box 168)
    - Pee (Box 168)
    - Peeves (Box 168)
    - Pen names (Box 168)
    - Pending reader questions (Box 168)
    - Pentagon - puzzle palace (Box 168)
    - Pentagon-ese (Box 168)
    - Penultimate (Box 168)
    - People like you (Box 168)
    - People power (Box 168)
    - People v persons (Box 168)
    - Perfect (Box 168)
    - Perfume lingo (Box 168)
    - Periodically (Box 168)
    - Permissiveness (Box 168)
    - Perp walk (Box 168)
    - Persian v Iranian (Box 168)
    - Persona (Box 168)
    - Personals (Box 168)
    - Peruse (Box 168)
    - Pet names (Box 168)
    - Pet peeves (Box 168)
    - Phat (Box 168)
    - Pheromone (Box 168)
    - Philadelphia-ese (Box 168)
    - Philadelphia-ese, 2 folders (Box 169)
    - Philo-American (Box 169)
    - Philologist - philanderer (Box 169)
    - Phishing (Box 169)
    - Phobias (Box 169)
    - Phone words (Box 169)
    - Phonecism (Box 169)
    - Phooey (Box 169)
    - Photo opportunity (Box 169)
    - Phrasedicks (Box 169)
    - Pi (Box 169)
    - Picture's worth a thousand words (Box 169)
    - Piddling (Box 169)
    - Pidgin (Box 169)
    - Piffle - flapdoodle - balderdash (Box 169)
    - Pigtown (Box 169)
    - Piñata (Box 169)
    - Place names (Box 169)
    - Plagiarism (Box 169)
    - Plain English (Box 169)
    - Planar (Box 169)
    - Planetary (Box 169)
    - Plangent (Box 169)
    - Pleaded v pled (Box 169)
    - Please v I need you (Box 169)
    - Plural of Times (Box 169)
    - Plurals (Box 170)
    - Plus (Box 170)
    - Plus up (Box 170)
    - Po-faced (Box 170)
    - Pocket of resistance (Box 170)
    - Pocketbook (Box 170)
    - Podium (Box 170)
    - Pods - ipod (Box 170)
    - Poetic Allusion Watch (PAW) (Box 170)
    - Pointer phrases (Box 170)
    - Points - flashpoint - breakpoint (Box 170)
    - Police lingo (Box 170)
    - Policy (Box 170)
    - Political (Box 170)
    - Political mainstream (Box 170)
    - Politically correct (PC) (Box 170)
    - Politics of inclusion - inclusiveness, 2 folders (Box 170)
    - Polyandry (Box 170)
    - Pomposities (Box 170)
    - Pool sprays (Box 170)
    - Pop songs (Box 170)
    - Pop-up (Box 170)
    - Pope terms (Box 170)
    - Popik, Barry (Box 170)
    - Populist (Box 170)
    - -porn (Box 170)
    - Pornographic words (Box 170)
    - Posh (Box 170)
    - Post partisan (Box 170)
    - Postal (Box 171)
    - Pothole (Box 171)
    - Potshot (Box 171)
    - Power curve (Box 171)
    - Practical v pragmatic (Box 171)
    - Practically (Box 171)
    - Practorial (Box 171)
    - Pre- (Box 171)
    - Prebuttal (Box 171)
    - Predominate/predominant (Box 171)
    - Preemptive/preventive (Box 171)
    - Prefixation - prefixes (Box 171)
    - Prepositions (Box 171)
    - Presenter (Box 171)
    - Presenter (Box 171)
    - Presents (Box 171)
    - President - capitalization (Box 171)
    - President-elect (Box 171)
    - President/presidency (Box 171)
    - Presidential speeches (Box 171)
    - Pressure (Box 171)
    - Prestigiate (Box 171)
    - Prestigious (Box 171)
    - Presumptive (Box 171)
    - Pretexting (Box 171)
    - Pretty penny (Box 171)
    - Pricey (Box 171)
    - Priest/priestess (Box 171)
    - Primal (Box 171)
    - Printer's devil (Box 171)
    - Prism (Box 171)
    - Prisoner (Box 172)
    - Priviligentsia (Box 172)
    - Proactive (Box 172)
    - Problematic/problemsome (Box 172)
    - Procter and Gamble, 2 folders (Box 172)
    - Product names (Box 172)
    - Profanity (Box 172)
    - Professional (Box 172)
    - Pronoun age (Box 172)
    - Pronoun agreement (Box 172)
    - Pronoun usage - transsexuals (Box 172)
    - Pronounce (Box 172)
    - Pronunciation, 2 folders (Box 172)
    - Proportionality (Box 172)
    - Pros/pro's (Box 172)
    - Prosha (Box 172)
    - Protest (Box 172)
    - Provided/providing (Box 172)
    - Psychobabble (Box 172)
    - Psychological jargon (Box 172)
    - Psychological warfare - psy-ops (Box 172)
    - Public intellectual (Box 173)
    - Publish and be damned (Box 173)
    - Publish or perish (Box 173)
    - Pucker factor (Box 173)
    - Pull out all the stops (Box 173)
    - Pull up our socks (Box 173)
    - Pulsing, 2 folders (Box 173)
    - Punctuation (Box 173)
    - Pundit (Box 173)
    - Puns (Box 173)
    - Purism (Box 173)
    - Push back (Box 173)
    - Push comes to shove (Box 173)
    - Putin, Vladimir - pronunciation (Box 173)
    - Q sans U (Box 173)
    - Qaddafi, Muammar (Box 173)
    - Qatar - pronunciation of (Box 173)
    - Qigong (Box 173)
    - Qualassurepurp (Box 173)
    - Quality (Box 173)
    - Quango (Box 173)
    - Quant (Box 173)
    - Quasi-mistakes (Box 173)
    - Que será será (Box 173)
    - Quebecois (Box 173)
    - Queer eye (Box 173)
    - Question mark v period (Box 174)
    - Queuing (Box 174)
    - Quickies (Box 174)
    - Quiescently (Box 174)
    - Quietism (Box 174)
    - Quotes (Box 174)
    - Racing slang (Box 174)
    - Railroads (Box 174)
    - Raked (Box 174)
    - Ramped up (Box 174)
    - Rant (Box 174)
    - Rat out (Box 174)
    - Rat race (Box 174)
    - Rationalize (Box 174)
    - Re (Box 174)
    - Read, Allen Walker (Box 174)
    - Reagan, Ronald - pronunciation (Box 174)
    - Reagan, Ronald - texts (Box 174)
    - Reaginisms (Box 174)
    - Real quick (Box 174)
    - Realignment (Box 174)
    - Realism (Box 174)
    - Really (Box 174)
    - Reason why (Box 174)
    - Reclama (Box 174)
    - Reconcilliation (Box 174)
    - Recovery (Box 174)
    - Recur (Box 174)
    - Recuse (Box 174)
    - Red line (Box 174)
    - Red meat (Box 174)
    - Red river Democrat (Box 174)
    - Redact (Box 174)
    - Redefinition (Box 174)
    - Redneck (Box 174)
    - Reduplication (Box 174)
    - Reflexisms (Box 174)
    - Regal wave (Box 174)
    - Regime v government (Box 175)
    - Regime v regimen (Box 175)
    - Regionalisms (Box 175)
    - Relationship (Box 175)
    - Remediate (Box 175)
    - Renascence (Box 175)
    - Rendition (Box 175)
    - Repellent v repulsive (Box 175)
    - Replicate v duplicate (Box 175)
    - Reprove v rebuke (Box 175)
    - Republican friends (Box 175)
    - Repurposing (Box 175)
    - Reset (Box 175)
    - Resource person (Box 175)
    - Retail politics (Box 175)
    - Retraction, 2 folders (Box 175)
    - Retronyms, 2 folders (Box 175)
    - Retroquotes (Box 175)
    - Revanche (Box 175)
    - Revenues (Box 175)
    - Reverse Reserve, The - misspellings (Box 175)
    - Reviewer-ese (Box 175)
    - Revisionist history (Box 175)
    - Revolution v revolt v uprising (Box 176)
    - Revulsion/repulsion (Box 176)
    - Rhetorical questions (Box 176)
    - Rhyme (Box 176)
    - Ride herd (Box 176)
    - Riff (Box 176)
    - Right side of history (Box 176)
    - Rise and shine (Box 176)
    - Road (Box 176)
    - Road map (Box 176)
    - Robot (Box 176)
    - Robust (Box 176)
    - Rock groups (Box 176)
    - Rock star (Box 176)
    - Rogers, Will (Box 176)
    - Rogue state (Box 176)
    - Role (Box 176)
    - Role model (Box 176)
    - Rolled (Box 176)
    - Rolling start (Box 176)
    - Rolodex ranger (Box 176)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore - speak softly and carry a big stick (Box 176)
    - Rope-a-dope (Box 176)
    - Roscoe (Box 176)
    - Rough sleepers (Box 176)
    - Round (Box 176)
    - RU-486 (Box 176)
    - Rumsfeld's rules (Box 176)
    - Run of the mill (Box 176)
    - Run the table (Box 176)
    - Running (Box 176)
    - Rush to judgment (Box 176)
    - Russian (Box 177)
    - Russian roulette (Box 177)
    - 's - disease (Box 177)
    - Saddam - pronunciation (Box 177)
    - SAFCO (Box 177)
    - Safe deposit box/ safety deposit box (Box 177)
    - SAFIRE - acronym (Box 177)
    - Safire - name (Box 177)
    - Salient (Box 177)
    - Salt water taffy (Box 177)
    - Salutations (Box 177)
    - Sanhedrin (Box 177)
    - Scandalmonger (Box 177)
    - Scantily clad (Box 177)
    - Scarf (Box 177)
    - Scat (Box 177)
    - Scatology (Box 177)
    - Scavenger hunt (Box 177)
    - Schizophrenic v schizoid (Box 177)
    - Schlemiel/schlimazel (Box 177)
    - Schlep (Box 177)
    - Schlub (Box 177)
    - Schlump (Box 177)
    - Schtick (Box 177)
    - Sci-fi (Box 177)
    - Science fiction antedates (Box 177)
    - Scintilla of doubt (Box 177)
    - Scorched earth (Box 177)
    - Scot free (Box 177)
    - Screen grab (Box 177)
    - Scribboleth - scriptonym - variants (Box 177)
    - Scrooched/scrunched (Box 177)
    - Scumbag (Box 177)
    - Second guess (Box 177)
    - Second tier (Box 177)
    - Secret plan (Box 178)
    - Secretary of Defense v Secretary of War (Box 178)
    - Sectarian (Box 178)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) - plan English (Box 178)
    - Security terms (Box 178)
    - Sedition (Box 178)
    - Seed (Box 178)
    - Seeded (Box 178)
    - Seeing someone (Box 178)
    - Seen (Box 178)
    - Seiner (Box 178)
    - Seized of the matter (Box 178)
    - Self- (Box 178)
    - Self-evident v self-apparent (Box 178)
    - Self-fulfilling prophecy (Box 178)
    - Sell-by date (Box 178)
    - Semantic infiltration (Box 178)
    - Semantic shift (Box 178)
    - Semicolon (Box 178)
    - Senator from - Hollings, Ernest (Box 178)
    - Send up (Box 178)
    - Serve/service (Box 178)
    - Service, 2 folders (Box 178)
    - Set the predicate (Box 178)
    - Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome (SARS) (Box 179)
    - Sex (Box 179)
    - Sex and Language Conference (Box 179)
    - Sex v gender (Box 179)
    - Sexed up (Box 179)
    - Sexism (Box 179)
    - Sexual favors (Box 179)
    - Sexual harassment (Box 179)
    - Sez you (Box 179)
    - Shadow Government (Box 179)
    - Shakespeare, William - most unkindest (Box 179)
    - Shakespeare, William - pith and moment v pitch and moment (Box 179)
    - Shall (Box 179)
    - Shall we say (Box 179)
    - Shatter (Box 179)
    - Sheidlower, Jesse (Box 179)
    - Shenanigans (Box 179)
    - Sherpa (Box 179)
    - Shoah (Box 179)
    - Shock and awe (Box 179)
    - Shocked, shocked (Box 180)
    - Shokku (Box 180)
    - Shop (Box 180)
    - Short strokes (Box 180)
    - Shout-out (Box 180)
    - Shovel ready (Box 180)
    - Show ankle (Box 180)
    - Show leg (Box 180)
    - Show me a loser (Box 180)
    - Show stopper (Box 180)
    - Showbiz terms (Box 180)
    - Showing up (Box 180)
    - Shred of evidence (Box 180)
    - Shrew (Box 180)
    - Sic (Box 180)
    - Sic 'em (Box 180)
    - Sic transit gloria mundi (Box 180)
    - Sick man of Europe (Box 180)
    - Side-step (Box 180)
    - Siegal, Al (Box 180)
    - Siege (Box 180)
    - Signal-ese - a-ok (Box 180)
    - Signal-ese - chest bump (Box 180)
    - Signal-ese - finger raising (Box 180)
    - Signal-ese - Hawaiian shaka (Box 180)
    - Signal-ese - horn honk (Box 180)
    - Signal-ese - how (Box 180)
    - Signal-ese - other (Box 181)
    - Signal-ese - salute (Box 181)
    - Signal-ese - Seinfeld (Box 181)
    - Signal-ese - thumbs up (Box 181)
    - Signal-ese - tip of the hat (Box 181)
    - Signal-ese - waggles (Box 181)
    - Signal-ese - you're welcome (Box 181)
    - Signature (Box 181)
    - Signs (Box 181)
    - Silver bullet, 2 folders (Box 181)
    - Similes (Box 181)
    - Simoleons (Box 181)
    - Simon, John (Box 181)
    - Simplistic (Box 181)
    - Simpson-ese (Box 181)
    - Sin (Box 181)
    - Singular v plural (Box 181)
    - Sink/sank/sunk (Box 181)
    - Sinners (Box 181)
    - Sino- (Box 181)
    - Sir Rudy - Giuliani, Rudolph (Box 181)
    - Situation (Box 181)
    - Situational (Box 181)
    - Skank (Box 181)
    - Skeevy (Box 181)
    - Skin in the game (Box 182)
    - Skosh (Box 182)
    - Slain (Box 182)
    - Slam-dunk (Box 182)
    - Slamming (Box 182)
    - Slang, 5 folders (Box 182)
    - Slanguage - Variety lingo (Box 182)
    - Slapstick (Box 182)
    - Sleaze (Box 182)
    - Sleeping giant (Box 182)
    - Sliding pond (Box 182)
    - Slime (Box 182)
    - Sliming (Box 182)
    - Slog (Box 183)
    - Sloppiness in e-mail (Box 183)
    - Slow lock (Box 183)
    - Slurs (Box 183)
    - Smart alec (Box 183)
    - Smash-mouth (Box 183)
    - Smell of greasepaint (Box 183)
    - Smitchik (Box 183)
    - Smoke and mirrors (Box 183)
    - Smoking gun (Box 183)
    - Snail mail (Box 183)
    - Snallygaster (Box 183)
    - Snarky (Box 183)
    - Snatch option (Box 183)
    - Sneak preview (Box 183)
    - So (Box 183)
    - So - as (Box 183)
    - So - starting sentences (Box 183)
    - So help me God (Box 183)
    - Soap opera (Box 183)
    - Sober second thought (Box 183)
    - Soccer mom (Box 183)
    - Soccer names (Box 183)
    - Soda straw (Box 183)
    - Soft dollars (Box 183)
    - Solana, Javier de (Box 183)
    - Solecisms (Box 183)
    - Something of the night (Box 183)
    - Sop to Cerberus (Box 183)
    - Soukhanov, Anne (Box 183)
    - Soup and fish (Box 183)
    - Southernisms (Box 183)
    - Soviets (Box 184)
    - Space (Box 184)
    - Space jargon (Box 184)
    - Spaces (Box 184)
    - Spanglish (Box 184)
    - Speculation (Box 184)
    - Speech (Box 184)
    - Speed bump (Box 184)
    - Spell-checker (Box 184)
    - Spelling, 5 folders (Box 184)
    - Spider hole (Box 185)
    - Spiffy (Box 185)
    - Spin him out (Box 185)
    - Spinmeister (Box 185)
    - Spinster (Box 185)
    - Spleissen v spalten (Box 185)
    - Split infinitives (Box 185)
    - Splitist (Box 185)
    - Spoiler (Box 185)
    - Spokes- (Box 185)
    - Spookspeak (Box 185)
    - Spoonfuls (Box 185)
    - Spork (Box 185)
    - Sports lingo (Box 185)
    - Spray (Box 185)
    - Sprezzatura (Box 185)
    - Spring of nations (Box 185)
    - Spruced up (Box 185)
    - Squad squad (Box 185)
    - Square one (Box 185)
    - Squirrely (Box 185)
    - Squushed (Box 185)
    - Stack is decked (Box 185)
    - Stage slang (Box 186)
    - Stalkerazzi (Box 186)
    - Stalking horse (Box 186)
    - Stan (Box 186)
    - Stanch/staunch (Box 186)
    - Stand down (Box 186)
    - Starter (Box 186)
    - Stash (Box 186)
    - State department dictionary (Box 186)
    - State of the union (Box 186)
    - Stay the course (Box 186)
    - Steely-eyed - spindly-legged (Box 186)
    - Stem winder (Box 186)
    - Stengel-ese - Stengel, Casey (Box 186)
    - Stent/stint (Box 186)
    - Step (Box 186)
    - Stickhandle (Box 186)
    - Stiff (Box 186)
    - Stock market-ese (Box 186)
    - Stolen meanings, 2 folders (Box 186)
    - Stovepiping - antonyms (Box 186)
    - Strait and narrow (Box 186)
    - Strangers (Box 186)
    - Strangers To the Tribe (Box 186)
    - Strategist, 2 folders (Box 187)
    - Strawman (Box 187)
    - Street (Box 187)
    - Street price (Box 187)
    - Strip alert (Box 187)
    - Stud-duck pundit (Box 187)
    - Stuff (Box 187)
    - Subject-verb agreement (Box 187)
    - Subjective v subjunctive (Box 187)
    - Subjunctive (Box 187)
    - Suboptimal (Box 187)
    - Substantially (Box 187)
    - Sucker (Box 187)
    - Sucks (Box 187)
    - Suffixes (Box 187)
    - Summer reads (Box 187)
    - Summit-ese (Box 187)
    - Super - hyper (Box 187)
    - Superdelegate (Box 187)
    - Superlatives (Box 187)
    - Superman (Box 187)
    - Suppeditate (Box 187)
    - Suppression - repression - oppression (Box 187)
    - Surfing (Box 187)
    - Surge (Box 187)
    - Surreal (Box 188)
    - Suspension of disbelief (Box 188)
    - Suss (Box 188)
    - Sweet and lowdown (Box 188)
    - Sweet spot (Box 188)
    - Sweetheart (Box 188)
    - Swift boat (Box 188)
    - Swiftie, Tom (Box 188)
    - Switch grass (Box 188)
    - Swivet (Box 188)
    - Synecdoche (Box 188)
    - Synergetic/synergistic (Box 188)
    - Synonym (Box 188)
    - Syntax (Box 188)
    - Syracuse - pronunciation (Box 188)
    - Systemic/systematic (Box 188)
    - T-shirts (Box 188)
    - Tabloid (Box 188)
    - Tacit rainbow (Box 188)
    - Tacky (Box 189)
    - Take one (Box 189)
    - Take the fifth (Box 189)
    - Talk show-ese (Box 189)
    - Talking heads (Box 189)
    - Talking points (Box 189)
    - Tamony, Peter (Box 189)
    - Tamony, Peter - head list, 3 folders (Box 189)
    - Tamper-evident - shelf-stable (Box 189)
    - Target of opportunity (Box 189)
    - Tarmac (Box 189)
    - Tarred and feathered (Box 189)
    - Tarted up (Box 189)
    - Tattoo regret (Box 189)
    - Tautophrases (Box 189)
    - Taxonomy (Box 189)
    - TBGBs - Blair, Tony and Brown, Gordon (Box 190)
    - Technical jargon (Box 190)
    - Tectonic (Box 190)
    - Teen lingo (Box 190)
    - Teeter, Karl V. (Box 190)
    - Tell it to the hand (Box 190)
    - Teller vote (Box 190)
    - Terrorist (Box 190)
    - Tex-mex language (Box 190)
    - Thanksgiving (Box 190)
    - Thanksgiving (Box 190)
    - , that (Box 190)
    - That (Box 190)
    - That's a wrap (Box 190)
    - That/which (Box 190)
    - That/who (Box 190)
    - The (Box 190)
    - Themeless pudding (Box 190)
    - Theocon (Box 190)
    - There you go (Box 190)
    - There's/there is/there are (Box 190)
    - Thesaurus (Box 190)
    - Third degree (Box 190)
    - Third force (Box 190)
    - Third guess (Box 190)
    - Third rail, 2 folders (Box 190)
    - Third world (Box 191)
    - This call may be monitored (Box 191)
    - This will not stand (Box 191)
    - Thought police (Box 191)
    - Thousand points of light (Box 191)
    - Three - III (Box 191)
    - Three sheets to the wind (Box 191)
    - Throughput - input - output (Box 191)
    - Thwart mode (Box 191)
    - Ticked off (Box 191)
    - Tickle the wire (Box 191)
    - Tiger by the tail (Box 191)
    - 'til/till (Box 191)
    - Time outout (Box 191)
    - Time-ese (Box 191)
    - Tin ear (Box 191)
    - Tinker's dam/tinker's damn (Box 191)
    - Tipping point, 2 folders (Box 191)
    - Title quoting (Box 191)
    - Titles (Box 191)